Finding Aid for John Ted Moffit papers, 1884-1947
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
John Ted Moffit papers 1884-1947
Moffit, John Ted, 1862-1947.
1 linear foot
87100 Aa 2
Alumnus of the Law School of the University of Michigan, and Iowa attorney; files relating to his alumni activities.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of John T. Moffit (donor no. 1415 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
John T. Moffit was a graduate of the Law School of the University of Michigan, Class of 1886. Following graduation, he became an attorney in Iowa. He was also active in alumni matters, especially reunions of his class. He was class secretary for a period of time.
The Moffit collection consists of correspondence and other papers largely relating to his activities as secretary of the class of 1886; include reunion materials, treasurer's files, membership materials, and miscellanea.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Dept. of Law.; University of Michigan. Dept. of Law. Class of 1886.
- Correspondence
  - 1909-1947 and undated, 10 folders (Box 1)
- University of Michigan Law School Class of 1886
  - Reunion Files
    - 1906 (Box 1)
    - 1911 (Box 1)
    - 1916, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1921, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1926, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1931, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - 1936, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - 1941 (Box 1)
  - Treasurer's Files
    - 1931 (Box 1)
    - 1936 (Box 1)
    - 1941 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Volume containing names of class members (with city of residence and occasional notes) (Box 1)